{
    "id": "7fc7336366e9499f9ee4cb661ac7e4bb",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She ……………………….. red and ran out of the room.",
            "description": "Turn is common before color words. It is used to talk about visible changes of state.",
            "answers": [
                "turned",
                "became",
                "grew"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Alice is the person ………………………… keeps a deer in the garden shed.",
            "description": "We use who to refer to people.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A deer is …………………………. Alice keeps in the garden shed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The baby’s eyes are not at all the same color ………………………… yours.",
            "description": "We can use the structure same …as to say that people or things are similar.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She looks ……………………. older than her daughter.",
            "description": "We can use no to modify a comparative word.",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "not",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t seen him ………………………… ages.",
            "description": "We use for to indicate duration.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "from",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Samuel and ………………………. decided to split up.",
            "description": "Contractions are not normally written with double subjects.",
            "answers": [
                "I have",
                "I've",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The village ……………………….. I live is very beautiful.",
            "description": "Where can mean that…in.",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If you have already had measles, you are unlikely to get …………………………… again.",
            "description": "The names of illnesses are usually uncountable in English and hence we use singular pronouns to refer back to them.",
            "answers": [
                "it",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have difficulty …………………………… dates.",
            "description": "The preposition ‘in’ can be dropped out after difficulty.",
            "answers": [
                "remembering",
                "in remembering",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandfather is eighty-five but he still enjoys ……………………….. health.",
            "description": "Health is an uncountable noun. We cannot use an article with it.",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "a good"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you bought the …………………………?",
            "description": "Although groceries is an uncountable noun, it has no singular form.",
            "answers": [
                "groceries",
                "grocery"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}